<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existing mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="123738" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Adjust Transit Capacity" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Increase/decrease Public Transit Depots + Total Passengers" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
### Adjust Transit Capacity (ATC)

#### Features
- **Transit depots:** change max vehicles per depot (Bus, Ferry, Subway, Taxi, Tram, Train)
- **Passengers:** change maximum seats (Bus, Tram, Train, Subway, Ship, Ferry, Airplane)

### Notes 🚍🚋🚆✈️🚢
- *Adjust Sliders* at any time, no restart needed; supports switching cities.
- *Depot capacity* = maximum number of vehicles a single depot can maintain/spawn (extension building not scaled).
- Avoid other depot/passenger capacity mods to avoid conflicts (they override each other).
- No Harmony patch or Reflection used; less likely to break on patch days.
- Safe to remove any time (use Reset buttons to return to vanilla game values).

### Important note
- ATC is a good fit for players who only want Transit features.
- The newer mod Public Works Plus (PwP) includes all of ATC plus 5 other sections combined (e.g. Industry Trucks + Deliveries).
- If installing PwP, then remove ATC (since ATC is included in PwP).
- ATC will get minor updates, but major new features will be in the PwP mod link. 
- If you want an option to reduce bus lines to 1 bus, get Public Works mod (All Vehicle Capacity).

### Support and feedback
- If the mod helps you, give it a Like, it's free + easy :)
- Feedback on: Github, Discord, etc., links on this page.

### Credits
- River-Mochi: author
- yenyang: code review and testing.
- transit part is inspired by Wayz's original Depot Capacity Changer.
- Necko1996: testing
- BugsyG: testing

### Performance
This is designed to *not* run in the city per-frame. Player makes changes in Options Menu > then mod goes idle.

### 11+ Languages

- English, Français, Deutsch, Español, Italiano, Polski Polish, Português Brazilian
- 한국어, 日本語, 简体中文 (Simplified Chinese), 繁體中文 Traditional Chinese, Turkish, Vietnamese

### Tip:
If you want to increase transit route slider a little more, add some stops to the route.
Game auto-increases the max based on different factors, adding stops is just the easiest to nudge it.

tags: city dispatch, control municipal, public transit system change size, increase people, depot size demand, decrease passengers

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail-ATC.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image10-Depots.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image20-Passengers.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/adjust-transit-capactiy.1866178/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.3.6" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!-- Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset -->
<ChangeLog>
- Updated for game patch 1.6
- Added Turkish and Vietnamese translations.
- removed Options menu Transit Line policy checkbox, Public Works mod has it.
- verbose log option now only in Debug build.
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
    <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/CS2-AdjustTransit" />
    <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/gwXgvtyhjc" />

</Publish>
